ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American Federation of Labor and Congress on Industrial Organizations: Officers, 1992-1993 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress on Industrial Organizations: Defense Fund, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1992-1995 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress on Industrial Organizations: Executive Council, 1991-1995 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Allied Industrial Workers, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Auto Parts Division, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  March 31 and June 29
- Amalgamated and Affiliates, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- American Institute For Free Labor Development, 1991-1995 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Aspen Institute, 1992-1995 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Automotive Parts Division, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Directories, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Barney's New York, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Mailings, 1991-1995 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Budgets, 1991-1995 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- New York City Central Labor Council, 1992-1995 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous, 1991-1995 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- City Performance Review Steering Committee Meeting, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1990-1991 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Abrams Campaign, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Actor, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiations, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Defense Fund, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Trade Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Common Trade File, Articles and Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Health Care Committee, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Bag and Packaging Conference Materials, 1990-1991 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Boys Choir of Harlem: Harlem Youth Development Foundation, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association: Clothing Negotiations, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- The Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1976-1978 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Harold and Sue Adel, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1974-1976 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Bank Holding Company Act, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- American Arbitration Association Mediation Advisory Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1972-1978 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- American Bar Association: Council Section of Labor Relations Law, 1974-1978 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- BANKAMERICARD, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- Boy Scouts: Board of Reviews, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Boy Scouts: Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Boy Scouts: Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Boy Scouts: Parent Letters, 1973-1976 (Box 113, Folder 12)
- Boy Scouts: Roster, 1972-1976 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Boy Scouts: Schedules and Tours, 1972-1975 (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Boy Scouts: Troop Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- Cornell Ad Hoc Committee on Capital Financing and Financial Planning, 1975-1978 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 17)
- Cornell: Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 18)
- Cornell University: Financial Profile, 1978-1979 (Box 113, Folder 19)
- Cornell: By-Laws, 1974-1977 (Box 113, Folder 20)
- Cornell: Committee on Commencement Arrangements, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 21)
- Cornell Contribution, 1975-1978 (Box 113, Folder 22)
- Cornell Convocation, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 23)
- Cornell Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 113, Folder 24)
- Cornell: Faculty Council Meeting, 1971-1978 (Box 113, Folder 25)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Convention, 1991-1993 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: International Affairs, 1991-1995 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Occupation Safety and Health (Box 114, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Organizing Institute, 1993 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Union Label, 1993-1995 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: Union Privilege, 1991-1995 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Bank of Chicago, 1993 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Cleaners and Dyers Insurance Fund Clothing, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  July 23
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1991-1994 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund Supplement Plan, 1992-1995 (Box 114, Folder 11)
- COTFUND Puerto Rico Sub-Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment Retirement Fund, 1991-1994 (Box 114, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Service Insurance and Allied Industries Fund (Box 114, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Fund, 1991-1995 (Box 114, Folder 15)
- American Arbitration Association, 1990-1995 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- The American Labor Museum, 1991-1994 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- American Organization for Rehabilitation through Training Federation, 1991-1994 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Americans for Peace Now, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Thank You America What Went Wrong, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Asian American Free Labor Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Morton Bahr Tribute, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Beck, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Big Yank, Incorporated, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Bidermann Industries Group, 1990-1993 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Bilderberg Meetings, 1990-1995 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Biltwell, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Ron Blackwell: Economic Affairs, 1991-1995 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Botany, 1992-1995 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- Boy Scouts of America, 1991-1995 (Box 115, Folder 15)
- British North American Committee, 1991-1994 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Agenda for Meeting of Executive Committee of Board of Trustees of Cornell University, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  January 25- 26, March 15, May 26, June 28, September 13
- Project Proposal to the Alfred Pritchard Sloan Foundation, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  August 31
- The German Industrial Relations System: Lessons for the United States?, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1994-1995 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Papers Prepared in Advance by Conference Presenters, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  March 14-15
- The Greif Companies, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  January 24
- The Diffusion of Human Resource Innovations: Lessons from the Apparel Industry, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Annual Report to Alfred Pritchard Sloan Foundation, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union - Proposals for Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1991-1994 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Jack Sheinkman's Remarks: Opening of Garment Negotiations, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  July 27
- Facts for Bargaining: Cotton Garment, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 10)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 11)
- Greif Companies/ Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1991-1993 (Box 117, Folder 12)
- Follow Up Action File, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 13)
- The Greif Companies/ Genesco, Incorporated/ Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 15)
- A Strategy for Innovation, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 16)
- Valuation of Bargaining Proposals, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  September 2
- Clothing Negotiations "1993" (Box 117, Folder 18)
- Bank Meeting, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 19)
- Irving Alter, Esquire, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 20)
- For Jack Sheinkman: St. Louis, 1992-1993 (Box 117, Folder 21)
- The Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 22)
- Facts for Bargaining: Clothing, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 23)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union: General Office, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union: Merger File, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  January 14
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Audited Financial Statements, 1990-1992 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union: Employee Benefit Structure, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Bargaining Units, by Joint Board and Directly Affiliated Locals, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  March 30
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Bargaining Unit Directory, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- Sample Agreements with Staff Unions (Box 118, Folder 7)
- Firm Information: Industry Sectors, Associations, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 8)
- Organizational and Administrative Departments (Box 118, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board: Member and Committees (Box 118, Folder 10)
- Organizational Structures: Addresses (Box 118, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Membership, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 12)
- Cotton Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box 118, Folder 13)
- The Report of the Twentieth Century Fund Task Force on Market Speculation and Corporate Governance, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 14)
- The Will to Act: Report of the Sub council on Corporate Governance and Financial Markets to the Competitiveness Policy Council, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 15)
- Time Horizons and Technology Investments, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 16)
- Capital Choices: Changing the Way America Invests in Industry (Box 118, Folder 17)
- Walraven File, 1991-1993 (Box 118, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1992-1993 (Box 118, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Financial Statements [1 of 3], 1991-1994 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  December 31
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Financial Statements [2 of 3], 1992-1993 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  April 30
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Financial Statements [3 of 3], 1992-1993 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  March 31
- Jack Sheinkman - Clothing, 1990-1991 (Box 118, Folder 23)
- Mission Statement and Proposed Budget for 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 25)
- Sheinkman, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 26)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board - Reading Packet, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 28)
- Mail Operations Department, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Communications Department, 1991-1995 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Buy American/ Complaint Letters, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Contributions, 1992-1995 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Colt, 1992-1993 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Corbin Limited, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Cornell Industrial and Labor Relations Campaign, 1994-1995 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Unedited Convention Proceedings, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  June 15-19
- The Seventh Joint Conference of Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: International Ladies' Garment Workers Union - Zensen, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  March 3-5
- The Philadelphia Joint Board Constitution (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Chicago and Central Regional Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Constitution of Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Cornell: Fiscal and Financing, Planning [1 of 2], 1975-1979 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Cornell: Fiscal and Financing, Planning [2 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Cornell: Funds, 1972-1973 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Cornell University Industrial and Labor Relations: General, 1975-1978 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Cornell University Industrial and Labor Relations: Advisory Council, 1973-1978 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- The Physical and Financial Condition of the New York Hospital: Cornell Medical Center, 1972-1973 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Report of the Trustee Ad Hoc Committee on the Status of Minorities, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  September 21 and October
- Cornell: State Relationships Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Cornell: State of Women, 1972-1974 (Box 121, Folder 9)
- Cornell: University Charter, 1972-1975 (Box 121, Folder 10)
- Cornell: Weinberg Seminar, 1967-1968 (Box 121, Folder 11)
- Report of the Health Planning Steering Committee, 1976 (Box 121, Folder 12)
- Cornell: Surveys, 1974-1976 (Box 121, Folder 13)
- E and B Supermarkets, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  March 13
- Eastern Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 15)
- Federation of Co-operatives, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: January to February, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: January to February Awaiting Reply, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: March to April, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: March to April Awaiting Reply, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: May to June, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: May to June Awaiting Reply, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: July to August, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: July to August Awaiting Reply, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: September to October, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: September to October Awaiting Reply, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: November, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: December, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: November to December Awaiting Reply, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: January, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: February, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: March, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: April, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: May, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: June, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: July, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: August, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: September, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: October, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: November, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: December, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: January, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: February, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: March, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: April, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: May, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: June, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: July, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: August, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: September, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: October, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: November, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: December, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: January, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: February, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: March, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: April, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: May, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: June, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: July, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: August, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: September, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: October, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: November, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: December, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 12)
- Medical/ Dental Forms (Box 126, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 126, Folder 2)
- The Yale Club Information Guide, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Department Directory, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  June 25
- Address Listings, 1981-1984 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1983 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- Cotton Negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box 126, Folder 7)
- Crafted with Pride in the United States of America, 1992-1994 (Box 126, Folder 8)
- Council on Economic Priorities, 1994-1999 (Box 126, Folder 9)
- Governor Mario Cuomo, 1990-1994 (Box 126, Folder 10)
- Cuomo Commission: Latin America Task Force, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 11)
- Cuomo Commission Two, 1990-1994 (Box 126, Folder 12)
- Council on Competiveness, 1993 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- Henrietta Dabney, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Daily News Strike, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 2)
- Employee Partnership Fund, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 3)
- Economic Policy Institute: North American Free Trade Agreement, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- Lichtenberg, 1990-1992 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1991-1993 (Box 128, Folder 6)
- National Labor Committee: Central America Correspondences, 1991-1993 (Box 128, Folder 7)
- National Committee for Labor Israel, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- British-North American Committee, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  June 18-20
- Endorsement for United States Tour of Haitian Labor Leader Chavonne Jean-Baptist, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  April 6
- Legal Department, 1991-1992 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- Governor's Commission on Competitiveness, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 12)
- Gray Davis, 1993-1995 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- Deep Springs, 1991-1995 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Deep Springs Economy, Health Insurance, 1992-1995 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Democratic National Committee, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  March 8
- Deep Spring Pension, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  January 23, 30
- Democratic Socialists of America, 1991-1994 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- Department Heads Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 129, Folder 7)
- Mission Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- David Dinkins (New York City Mayor), 1990-1993 (Box 129, Folder 9)
- Economic Policy Council: International Labor Organization and the Global Economy, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 10)
- Earle Industries, 1993-1994 (Box 129, Folder 11)
- Economic Policy Council Steering Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 129, Folder 12)
- Economic Strategy Institute, 1993-1995 (Box 129, Folder 13)
- Economic Policy Council of the United Nations Association, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 14)
- Economic Policy Institute, 1991-1995 (Box 129, Folder 15)
- Education Department, 1991-1995 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Ellis Island Awards, 1992-1994 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Harry Lautman Engineering Department, 1990-1993 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Ergonomics, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Farah, 1991-1994 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Farris Fashion, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR), 1990-1995 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade: Gang of Six, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  March 23
- Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade: Legislation, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- Bernie Firestone, 1989-1993 (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Fingerhut, 1992-1994 (Box 131, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Assorted Files, 1991-1995 (Box 131, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 131, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board Employer Participation, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board January, 1992-1994 (Box 131, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board February, 1994-1995 (Box 131, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board May, 1992-1994 (Box 131, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board September, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board November, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board Resolutions, 1994 (Box 131, Folder 19)
- Local 340, 1979-1995 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Locals General Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Industrial Union Department Committees and Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- Italian American Labor Council, 1991-1994 (Box 132, Folder 4)
- International Rescue Committee, 1995 (Box 132, Folder 5)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1991-1994 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- International Labor Office, 1991-1995 (Box 132, Folder 7)
- International Labor Rights Educational Research Fund, 1990-1994 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- International Chemical and Energy Workers Federation, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Health Care, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 10)
- Arthur Gundersheim, 1990-1995 (Box 132, Folder 11)
- Guatemala Labor Education Project, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 12)
- Gittman Brothers, 1992 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  November 11
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 132, Folder 14)
- The Forum, 1993-1994 (Box 132, Folder 15)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1990-1993 (Box 132, Folder 16)
- Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 17)
- Financial Democracy Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 18)
- Finance Department, 1991-1994 (Box 132, Folder 19)
- Committee on Political Education, 1991-1993 (Box 132, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund [1 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund [2 of 2], 1993 (Box 133, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (CLOFUND), 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company [1 of 4], 1993 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  November 30. December 10, 16.
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company [2 of 4], 1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company [3 of 4], 1993 (Box 133, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company [4 of 4], 1993 (Box 133, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company Chargebacks, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 10)
- The Segal Company, 1990-1992 (Box 133, Folder 11)
- Financial Reporting Package, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund (CLOFUND) Meetings and Amalgamated Life Insurance Company Meetings, 1991 (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund (COTFUND) Meetings, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund Board Members and Trustees, 1991 (Box 134, Folder 3)
- Minutes of the Executive Council of the America Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  May 5 - 6
- Occupational Health Foundation: Board of Directors' Meeting, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  February 20